SETH EUGENE WILLS



CONTACT

(918)384-8280



seth.eugene@icloud.com (



Kansas City, MO



www.linkedin.com/in/seth-eugene (in)



EDUCATION

ASSOCIATES IN ARTS COFFEYVILLE COMMUNITY COLLEGE

> WEB DEVELOPMENT CERTIFICATE UNIVERSITY OF KANSAS

SKILLS

I have ten years of combined customer service experience. I know and love coffee and always want to learn more. I like people and people like me. I have a class B CDL, food handlers card, and liquor permit. The service industry is what I love, and I'm good at it. I'm always happy to offer my computer or photography knowledge. I'm excited to meet you, thanks for your time!

INTRODUCTION

The service industry has prepared me for whatever is next. Humans are the constant in everything we do, and I've spent the last ten years learning how to best relate to others in professional settings. Everything from cashier to caregiver to photographer, I've done it. Not only have these positions taught me how to relate with others, but they have also taught me how to enjoy them. I really love working with people, and I know this love will continue to serve me well in the next steps of my life.

WORK EXPERIENCE

BON BON

SERVER MANAGER MAY 2017 - OCTOBER 2018

As a manager at Bon Bon my duties include; product quality control, keeping an inviting atmosphere, talking to customers with complaints, and ensuring an appropriate number of staff are on duty during shift.

PRIME EDITS

SENIOR PHOTO EDITOR/ CUSTOMER SATISFACTION JULY 2016 - JULY 2018

I edited professional photographers work using the Adobe suite. We also managed clients social media accounts. Keeping in contact with the clients and what they wanted from the editors was the largest part of the job.

APPLE INC.

SALES / TECHNICIAN NOVEMBER 2015-JULY 2016

I helped customers' non-functioning devices. Much of my job was deescalating upset customers and providing a positive experience to everyone who walked in.

CHIMERA CAFE

BARISTA / BARTENDER / SERVER FEBRUARY 2013 - NOVEMBER 2015

Duties included prepping recipes when supplies ran out, making orders, and deciding on ratios for every coffee that came in. Of course the biggest part of this position was maintaining an inviting atmosphere.

SETH EUGENE PHOTOGRAPHY

I also run my own side photography business. I mainly focus on family portraits but also do some commercial work and weddings when the opportunities arise. Check out setheugenephoto.com to see some of my work.